http://www.barbarabrennan.com/privacy-policy

AboutAbout barbaraFacultyAbout barbaraFaculty TrainingsGetting Started (FAQs)Programs and locationsStudent CalendarGetting Started (FAQs)Programs and locationsStudent Calendar Workshops & EventsWorldwide eventsCampus workshopsWorldwide eventsCampus workshopsFind a practitionerStoreRequest informationTranslate  AboutAbout barbaraFacultyAbout barbaraFaculty TrainingsGetting Started (FAQs)Programs and locationsStudent CalendarGetting Started (FAQs)Programs and locationsStudent Calendar Workshops & EventsWorldwide eventsCampus workshopsWorldwide eventsCampus workshopsFind a practitionerStoreRequest informationTranslate Privacy policyYour
privacy is important to us. It is Barbara Brennan School of Healing's
policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
from you across our website, https://barbarabrennan.com, and other sites we own and operate.We only ask for personal information when we truly need it to provide
a service to you. We collect it by fair and lawful means, with your
knowledge and consent. We also let you know why we’re collecting it and
how it will be used.We only retain collected information for as long as necessary to
provide you with your requested service. What data we store, we’ll
protect within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft,
as well as unauthorised access, disclosure, copying, use or
modification.We don’t share any personally identifying information publicly or with third-parties, except when required to by law.Our website may link to external sites that are not operated by us.
Please be aware that we have no control over the content and practices
of these sites, and cannot accept responsibility or liability for their
respective privacy policies.You are free to refuse our request for your personal information,
with the understanding that we may be unable to provide you with some of
your desired services.Your continued use of our website will be regarded as acceptance of
our practices around privacy and personal information. If you have any
questions about how we handle user data and personal information, feel
free to contact us.This policy is effective as of 23 August 2019.Student PortalAlumni PortalFaculty PortalPrivacy PolicyCopyright ©2020 Barbara Brennan School of Healing. All Rights Reserved. Licensed by the Florida Commission for Independent Education - License No. 2897AboutAbout barbaraFacultyTrainingsGetting Started (FAQs)Programs and locationsStudent CalendarWorkshops & EventsWorldwide eventsCampus workshopsFind a practitionerStoreTranslate
